http://www.knicksonline.com/privacy-policy/

Pin It
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit KnickOnline.com?
When registering on our forums (www.knicksonline.com/forums), as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our forum or enter information on our site.
Provide us with feedback on our products or services
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, surf the website, or use certain other site features only to notify you upon certain details you have agreed on (receiving a private message, a reply to one of your posts was added)
How do we protect your information?
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
All sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party links
The homepage and some articles we publish may contain links to articles from third parties. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
â€¢ Remarketing with Google AdSense
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Created February 25th, 2017
Crash the boards
2020 NBA Draft: NYK target a PG (129 replies)Knicks Insider: "All Things Knicks" (681 replies)NBA Restart:
Are you watching??! Let’s discuss!!! (51 replies)Other NBA games and League (1446 replies)Hire Tom Thibodeau (255 replies)Bucks boycott Wed. playoff game (7 replies)Happy Birthday, rady!!! (5 replies)Forums home
NBA Teams
Featured articles
Tom Thibodeau to sign a 5 year deal as Knicks head-coach
After numerous weeks of searches and interviews, the Knicks finally got their man for the head-coach position, as Adrian...
Mitchell Robinson scores career-high as the Knicks beat the Bulls
Knicks beat the Pistons 95-92, win fourth straight in years
Steve Mills is no longer the Knicks president
Knicks, Nets play a regular season game as Madison Square Garden pays tribute to Kobe Bryant
Home
About
News
Knicks Roster 2019-20
Knicks Schedule 2019-20
Knicks Player Salaries
Knicks Player Stats 2019-2020
Forums
Knicks store
Contact
Copyright Â© 2001-2020 KnicksOnline.com / Made in Romania by Radu ROSCA (rady)
Knicks Online is a fan site and we have no affiliation or connection with the NBA or the New York Knicks. ( Privacy policy | Disclaimer ) To get in touch with the club management, please visit the official website - nyknicks.com.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkNoRead about cookies
